{
    "subject": "Marco_Ferreri",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Break_Up__film_",
    "human_readable": "Marco Ferreri directed the film Break Up.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9367310404777527,
            "question": "Which film was directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8432125449180603,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8018319010734558,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Break Up'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7084911465644836,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4550629258155823,
            "question": "Where did Marco Ferreri get his training in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.406688928604126,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Break Up' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3774176836013794,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of the film 'Break Up'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29373279213905334,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Break Up' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2585735619068146,
            "question": "Has the film 'Break Up' won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17242972552776337,
            "question": "What other films are similar to 'Break Up' in theme or style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marco Ferreri directed the film Break Up.",
            "html": "yago_8387_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has the film 'Break Up' won any awards?",
            "html": "yago_8387_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Break Up' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_8387_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the plot of the film 'Break Up'?",
            "html": "yago_8387_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8387_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The document with file path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8387/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt\" mentions that \"Break Up is a very rare movie shot by Marco Ferreri in the early '60s...\" which indicates that Marco Ferreri directed the film Break Up."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Marco Ferreri directing the film \"Break Up,\" which confirms the statement that Marco Ferreri directed the film \"Break Up.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}